Hello.
哈囉
I love my new job!
我愛死我的新工作了！
- Honey, you're screaming. - You bet your ass I am!
-親愛的，你在吼叫 -你說的沒錯，我就是！
I just had the best first day ever!
這工作是有史以來最棒的！
The kitchen? Twice as big as Allessandro's.
那個廚房，比之前的餐廳大兩倍…
Oh, that's great.
喔，太棒了
And clean? Not just health department-clean, Monica-clean!
說到乾淨，不只是符合衛生局標準 是莫妮卡式的乾淨！
Awesome.
酷斃了
Oh, and the people are so nice.
喔，還有同事都很好
There's this one guy, Jeffrey, he's the maitre d'.
有一個男的叫傑佛瑞 他是餐廳領班
Chandler, you will love him!
錢德，你會很喜歡他的！
He is without a doubt the funniest guy I have ever met!
毫無疑問他是我遇過最風趣的男人了！
The One With The Male Nanny
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
- This is nice. - I know.
-這真棒 -我知道
- You need both hands for that? - Yeah, I kind of do.
-你需要兩隻手才打得開？ -是啊，應該是要
Well, how's this?
嗯，那這樣呢？
Are you sure that's sweet enough?
你確定那樣夠甜嗎？
Look at you two holding hands.
瞧瞧你們兩個 手握著手
Is this getting serious?
是不是開始認真了呢？
Have you not talked about it yet?
你們有沒有談過了呢？
Am I making you uncomfortable?
我是不是讓你們很不舒服呢？
If you were bigger you'd hit me.
如果你再高壯一點你就會扁我了 對不對？
I'm sorry.
不好意思
It's obviously way too early for us to be having that conversation.
很明顯地現在就討論那種事 對我們而言是太早了
- Is it? - Maybe not. Is it?
-會嗎？ -或許不會，會嗎？
When I got divorced..
當我離婚後…
I didn't think I'd feel this way about someone for a really long time.
有一段很長的時間 我不認為會對任何人有這種感覺
Then again, I didn't think I'd meet someone like you. And..
而且，我也不認為會 遇到像你這樣的人…
This may be crazy-soon, but I want you to have this.
這或許太瘋狂快速了 但我希望給你這個
No, not.. That's gum.
不，不是…那是口香糖
Oh, five bucks! I love it when that happens, you know?
喔，五塊錢！ 我超喜歡這種事發生的，你知道嗎？
- You don't know it's there.. - I know. Keep digging.
-你不知道那裡有… -我知道，繼續挖
Sorry.
抱歉
It's a key.
是一隻鑰匙
To be honest, I think I'd prefer the five dollars.
老實說，我想我寧可要那五塊錢
- It's to my apartment. - Wow!
-我公寓的鑰匙 -哇！
Big step for Phoebe and Mike.
菲比跟麥克 兩人關係的一大步
I don't want you to feel like you have to give me your key..
我不希望你覺得這樣 你也要給我你的鑰匙
- No, I want to. - Thank God.
-不，我要 -感謝上帝
Wow. I was starting to think I'd never meet someone that..
哇，我本來還在想 我應該不會遇到一個人…
I wanted to do this with.
讓我想要這樣做的
Here you go.
拿去吧！
- This is cool. - It really is.
-這太酷了 -真的是很酷
I know it. It is amazing. These little things open doors!
我知道，太驚人了 這些小東西可以把門打開！
So I don't go back to work for another four weeks..
我四星期之後才需要回去上班…
but we would like our nanny to start right away..
但是我們希望我們的保姆可以馬上上班
so that Emma could get a chance to know her.
那艾□才有時間熟悉她
I think that's really smart.
我想這樣做是很聰明的
The easier we can make the transition for her the better.
我們換手過程越流暢對她越好
That's great. Great.
太棒了，很好
- So do you have any questions for us? - Not really.
-那你有沒有其他的問題想問我們呢？ -沒有
All right. Well, thank you so much for coming.
好了，那謝謝你跑這麼一趟
- Thank you. - It was really nice to meet you.
-謝謝 -很高興認識你
- We will call you. - Oh, you know, wait.
-我們會打電話給你 -喔，等一下…
I do have one question.
我是有一個問題
Do you guys do random drug testing?
你們會不定期對人做毒品測試嗎？
Boy, we hadn't really thought of that.
天啊，我們還真的沒想過這個
That's cool. But if you do, I'm gonna need three days' notice.
沒關係，但是如果你們要求要做 我需要你們提前三天告訴我
Okey-dokey!
好的，沒問題！
We're never gonna find a nanny.
我們永遠都找不到保姆了
Come on, Rach. We will. I promise. We have more interviews.
別這樣，瑞秋，我保證我們會找到的 我們還有其他的面試
Worse comes to worst, we can always reconsider the first one we met with.
情況不可能再更糟 我們總是可以重新考慮第一個人選
- What, the blond with no bra? - She was blond?
-什麼？那個沒穿胸罩的金髮女郎嗎？ -她的頭髮是金色的嗎？
Just a sec.
等一下
Okay, this one's name is Sandy.
好的，這個叫做珊帝
She's got a degree in Early Childhood Education.
她有幼兒教育學位
She worked for her last family for three years.
她在上個工作的家庭做了三年
Hi. I'm Sandy.
嗨，我是珊帝
And she's a little mannish.
而且她看起來有點男性化
Oh, my God! David!
喔，我的天！大衛！
- Is this a bad time? - No, it's a great time! Come in!
-現在會打擾你嗎？ -不，現在很好！進來吧！
Wow! Hi!
哇！嗨！
Oh, my gosh! What are you doing here? Are you back from Minsk?
喔，天啊！你在這裡做什麼呢？ 你從明斯克回來嗎？
Just for a couple of days.
只回來幾天
I'm here to explain to the people who gave us our grant..
我是回來跟提供補助款的人解釋…
why it's a positive thing that we've spent all their money..
為什麼我們花光了所有他們給的錢…
and accomplished nothing.
什麼都沒有做出 可以是件正面的事
Who cares? It got you here.
誰在乎呢？反正你回來了
It got me to New York. Then I got in a cab at the airport..
我回到紐約，然後在機場叫了部計程車
and the guy said, "Where to?"
司機問我要去哪？
I just gave him your address. I didn't even think about it.
我想都沒想就給了他你的地址
Where's your luggage?
你的行李呢？
Damn it.
該死
All right, I'll call the cab company.
好了，我來打電話給計程車行
We can call them later. Can you just stand there for a moment?
我們可以等一下再打 你可以先站在那邊一下子嗎？
Boy.
天啊
There's an old Russian expression that goes:
有一句俄羅斯老諺語是這樣的
Roughly translated, that means:
大略的翻譯就是：
"This thing that I'm looking at: Wow."
「我現在盯著的東西，哇！」
Thank you.
謝謝你
You should see me when.. Actually, no, I look pretty good.
你應該看看當我… 事實上，不用，我看起來挺不錯的
Are you kidding?
你在開玩笑嗎？
You know, when you don't see someone for a long time..
你知道的，當很久沒有見到一個人…
you build them up in your head, you start thinking:
你會在腦海中建立起這個人的影像 然後開始想
"Come on, don't be crazy, nobody's that beautiful."
「少來了，別發神經了 沒有人是那樣美的」
But, well, you are.
但是，嗯，你真的就是那樣美
Well, so are you seeing anyone?
那麼，你現在有在跟誰交往嗎？
No.
沒有
I'm just the worst person ever!
我是最糟糕的人！
How can I not tell David that I'm seeing Mike?
我怎麼可以不告訴大衛 我跟麥克在一起呢？
Maybe he didn't give you a chance.
或許他沒有給你機會說
He said, "Are you seeing someone?" and I said, "No."
他問我有沒有跟誰交往，而我說沒有
Well, that would've been your window.
喔，那本來是你可以澄清的機會的
I mean, I don't know. I was looking in his eyes..
我真的不知道，我看著他的雙眼…
and I was just thinking, "Oh, my God, it's David. David's here."
然後只能想 「我的天！是大衛，大衛在這裡」
He's so irresistible.
他真是令人無法抗拒
- Really? The scientist guy? - Really? Chandler?
-真的嗎？那個科學家？ -真的嗎？錢德？
Continue.
繼續說
Then it gets worse..
然後越來越糟糕…
because I told him I would see him tomorrow night.
因為我答應他明晚跟他見面
- Phoebe! - I know! Evil!
-菲比！ -我知道！邪惡的女人！
I like Mike so much, you know? It's just going really well. Oh, my God!
我真的好喜歡麥克，你知道嗎？ 發展得真的很順利，我的天！
Isn't it ironic that David would show up..
大衛出現在你跟麥克 交換鑰匙的同一天…
on the same day that you and Mike exchange keys?
這真是很諷刺嗎？
Yeah. You know, and given my lifelong search for irony..
是啊，而且你知道我一輩子都在 找尋諷刺的事…
you can imagine how happy I am!
你可以想像的到我有多開心！
- What are you gonna do? - I mean, I guess I just have to..
-你要怎麼辦呢？ -我想我只能…
tell David that nothing can happen between us.
告訴大衛我們之間是不可能的
Unless I don't.
除非我不用告訴他
You know, complicated moral situation?
你知道的，複雜的道德情況…
- No right, no wrong? - You have to tell David.
-是沒有錯或對 -你必須要告訴大衛
I knew I should've had this conversation with Joey.
我就知道我應該去問喬伊才對
Funniest guy she's ever met.
她遇過最風趣的男人…
I'm funny, right?
我很風趣，不是嗎？
What do you know? You're a door.
你知道個什麼？你只是一道門
You just like knock-knock jokes.
你就像是「敲敲門」笑話
Save it for inside.
等到裡面再發揮
So Oklahoma's a crazy place. You know, they call it the Sooner State.
奧克拉荷馬真是瘋狂 他們把那裡稱為早到者之州
Frankly, I'd sooner be in any other state!
事實上，我還真希望 可以早點離開到其它的州！
And what's with Oklahoma having a panhandle?
而且奧克拉荷馬 為什麼有個平底鍋柄呢？
Can all states have stuff like that?
其它的州可以有像那樣的東西嗎？
Hey, yeah, I'm from the waistband of Wyoming.
嘿，我是從懷俄明的中腰部來的
But when I was 7, we headed over to the crotch.
但是當我七歲的時候 我們就搬到胯下部了
Was your cabin pressurized?
你的機艙是不是有加壓呢？
And don't get me started on the way the people from Tulsa talk.
而且不要讓我開始告訴你們 土爾沙人說話的方式…
Okay.
好的
What's with the word "y'all"? You know, just two words just pushed together?
「你全」到底是個什麼字呢？ 只不過是「你們」跟「全部」加在一起
Are we all allowed to do that? Because if so, I say why stop there?
我們可以那樣做嗎？ 因為如果可以，還有很多字可以這樣玩
You know, your new poodle could be your noodle.
你的「新獅子狗」 可以變成你的「新獅」
And fried chicken could be fricken.
「油炸雞塊」可以變成「炸塊」
Waiter? Waiter, excuse me, I'll have the fricken!
服務生？服務生，不好意思 我想要點「炸塊」！
See, that's funny with the fricken, right?
瞧，「炸塊」很好笑吧？
No, it just reminds me of something this guy did today at work.
不，只是讓我想起今天工作時 有個人講的笑話…
I told you about that funny guy, Jeffrey, right?
我有跟你提過一個風趣的人叫做傑佛瑞 對嗎？
Yeah, he came up.
是啊，你提過
Well, he did this bit. You probably had to be there..
嗯，他做了一件事 你應該要在現場才感受的到…
but it was Liza Minnelli locked in our freezer eating a raw chicken.
莉莎明妮莉被鎖在冰箱裡面吃生雞肉
- Were you there? - No, but it sounds fricken funny.
-你在現場嗎？ -沒有，但是聽起來「炸塊」好笑
I really understand how hard it's gotta be to leave your child with another person.
我真的可以理解要把孩子交付給 另一個人是很困難的事
I mean, it's like leaving behind a piece of your heart.
我是說，這就像把心上的一塊肉割下
Sandy, that's exactly what it is.
珊帝，這正是如此
Are you gay?
你是同性戀嗎？
I'm sorry, that's our Ross. He's just Mr. Shoot Straight From The Hip.
我很抱歉，這就是我們的羅斯 他總是直言不諱
It's okay. I get that a lot doing what I do.
沒關係，我的工作常引來誤會
But I am straight. I'm engaged, actually.
但我不是同性戀，事實上我已經訂婚
- Her name's Delia. - That's pretty.
-她的名字叫做狄莉亞 -真是好名字
So you're just, like, a guy who's a nanny.
所以你只是一個當保姆的男人
I realize how it's a bit unorthodox for some people.
我知道這對一些人來說是很顛覆傳統的
But I really believe the most satisfying thing you can do with your life..
但我真的相信一生中最令人感到滿足的事情
is take care of a child.
就是照顧小孩子
Okay.
好的
Like at my last job.
就像我上一個工作…
I met Daniel when he was 3 weeks old.
我在丹尼爾三星期大的時候就認識他
And I got to watch him grow into this awesome person.
然後我看著他成長變成一個很棒的人
When I left, I said, "I'll see you soon."
當我離開的時候，我說： 「希望很快再見到你」
And he said to me, "Skadandy?"
然後他說「珊卡丹帝」
That was his name for me.
那是他給我的名字
"I'll see you every day right in.."
「我每天都會看到你在…」
- It's okay. - Yeah, kids say all kinds of crap.
-沒關係 -是啊，小孩子儘是會說些鬼話
Oh, God, she must need her diaper changed.
喔，天啊，她一定是需要換尿布了
- I can take care of that, if you want. - That would be great.
-我可以幫你處理，如果你要的話 -太棒了
Just so you know, these dinosaur toys aren't really age-appropriate.
順便跟你說一下，那些恐龍玩具 可能不適合她的年齡
They're mine.
那些是我的
Also not age-appropriate.
同樣也是不適齡
I love him, I love him, I love him!
我愛他，我愛他，我愛他！
Come on. Rach, he's a guy!
別這樣，瑞秋，他是個男人！
So what? He's smart. He's qualified.
那又如何？他很聰明，資歷又符合
Give me one good reason we shouldn't try him out.
給我一個理由為什麼我們不能試用他
Because it's weird!
因為這實在太奇怪了！
Why?
為什麼？
Wow, I never looked at it that way.
哇，我從來都沒有那樣想過
What kind of a job is that for a man? A nanny?
男人做那種工作像話嗎？保姆？
I mean, it's like if a woman wanted to be..
我是說，那就像一個女人想要成為…
Yes?
什麼？
King?
國王？
I hope you don't mind. I used some of my homemade lotion on Emma.
我希望你不介意，我在艾□身上 用了我自製的乳液
It's a mixture of calendula and honey cream. It'll dry that rash right up.
那是混合金盞花跟蜂蜜的乳液 對紅疹是立竿見影的
Plus, it keeps the hands young.
而且，使雙手保持年輕
Yes! Sandy, you're hired!
是的！珊帝，你被錄取了！
That's great!
太棒了！
I'm sorry.
不好意思
It's just such an emotional thing when you're welcomed into a new family.
只是被歡迎加入一個新家庭 是一件很令人感動的事
Oh, God. Come here.
喔，天啊，過來這裡
You gotta be at least bi.
你至少也是雙性戀
《大胸部女人》
I need you to set me up for a joke.
我需要你幫忙 讓我講笑話…
When Monica's around, ask me about fire trucks.
當莫妮卡在的時候，問我消防車怎樣
I don't know, Chandler. I'm not so good with remembering lines.
我不知道，錢德，我不是很會記台詞的
Thank God your livelihood doesn't depend on it.
感謝上帝你不是靠記台詞吃飯的
I know, right?
我知道，棒吧？
Why are we doing this?
我們為什麼要這樣做呢？
Monica says that her maitre d' is the funniest guy she's ever met.
莫妮卡說他們餐廳的領班 是她遇過最風趣的男人
- Seriously? She actually said that? - Yes. Am I crazy to be this upset?
-真的嗎？她真的那樣說？ -是的，我這樣不爽很瘋狂嗎？
- No! Being funny's your thing! - Yeah!
-不！風趣是你的專利！ -是啊！
Without that, you just got "lame with women"!
沒有了它，你還有什麼吸引女人的！
Hi! There you are.
嗨！你們都在
Fire trucks!
消防車！
- Hi. - Hi.
-嗨 -嗨
I brought you this from Minsk.
我從明斯克帶回來這個給你
You're not gonna belief this. This is lemon-flavored vodka.
你不會相信的，這是檸檬口味的伏特加
Yeah, we actually have this here.
是嗎？事實上這裡也有
I traded four pairs of Levi's for that.
我用四條牛仔褲換來的
Thanks anyway.
謝謝你
Wow. You look even more beautiful than you did yesterday.
哇，你看起來比昨天更美麗
In fact, I'm going to kiss you now.
事實上，我現在要親你
- Wait, wait. - I can't get away with stuff like that.
-等等… -我就是沒有辦法…
It sounded sexy in my head, so I..
在我腦海中聽起來很性感，所以我…
No, no, it's not that.
不，不，不是那件事
Remember when you asked me if I was seeing someone and I said no?
你記得當你問我有沒有跟誰交往 而我說沒有嗎？
Well, I am. His name's Mike.
事實上我有，他叫做麥克
- I should've told you. - No.
-我應該早點告訴你的 -不用…
Well, yeah.
嗯，你應該要的
I'm sorry. I wanted to tell you, but then I just got lost in your eyes..
我很抱歉，我想告訴你 但是我又沉醉在你的眼神中…
and I just forgot all about..
然後我就完全忘了…
- Mike? - Right, yes.
-麥克？ -是的，沒錯
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry. - Well, it's okay. I understand.
-我很抱歉，我很抱歉 -沒關係，我可以理解
Well, are you happy with this guy?
那，你跟這個人在一起快樂嗎？
- I am happy. - Damn it.
-我是很快樂 -該死
I'm sorry. I don't mean that. I want you to be happy.
我很抱歉，我不是那個意思 我要你過得快樂
But only with me. No, that's not fair. Who cares. Leave him.
但是只能跟我，不，那並不公平 管他的，拋棄他吧！
I don't mean that. Yes, I do. I'm sorry.
我不是那個意思，是的，我是 我很抱歉
I think I should probably go.
我想我應該離開了
But, David, I just want you to know that, you know..
但是，大衛，我只想要你知道…
telling you this is one of the hardest things I've ever had to do.
跟你坦白 是我做過最困難的事
Well, just so you know..
嗯，讓你知道一下…
hearing it wasn't exactly a Vladnik carnival, either.
聽到這件事也不像在過嘉年華
- Can we at least hug goodbye? - Of course. Yeah.
-我們至少可以擁抱道別吧？ -當然，可以
You know, and a kiss on the cheek wouldn't be totally inappropriate.
你知道的，在臉頰上親一下 應該不會是太不適當
- No. No. - I mean..
-不，不 -我是說…
- In Minsk? - Yeah?
-在明斯克… -怎樣呢？
It's two on each cheek..
是在兩邊各親兩下…
- and one on the lips. - Well, if that's what they do in Minsk.
-還有一下親在唇上 -嗯，好吧，如果那是明斯克的習俗
In New York, it's..
在紐約，是…
Oh, boy.
喔，天啊
Is everything all right?
一切都還好吧？
Oh, yeah. No, it's fine. It's fine.
喔，是的，很好，很好
Sandy was just telling me about how he proposed to his fiancee..
珊帝只是在告訴我他是如何 跟他未婚妻求婚的…
and it was so beautiful.
實在是太夢幻了
Her favorite flower is the camellia. From the poem..
她最喜歡的花是山茶花 從那首詩…
I can't hear it again!
我沒辦法再聽一次
You know, I can't tell it again!
我也沒辦法再說一次
And I'm fine never having heard it.
而我也還好不用聽到
- Rach, can I see you for a sec? - Yeah. Excuse me.
-瑞秋，我可以跟你說一下話嗎？ -好啊，失陪了
Do you realize that man has cried in our apartment three times?
你有發現那男人在我們家 已經哭過三次了嗎？
I haven't cried that many times since I moved in!
我從搬進來之後也沒哭過那麼多次！
Come on, Ross, you got a little misty when Ben broke your I-heart-fossils mug.
別這樣，羅斯，當班打破你的 「我愛化石」馬克杯，你也哭了啊！
I'll have you know that was a farewell gift from my colleagues at the museum.
那個馬克杯可是博物館同事 送我的離別禮物
- Okay? They all chipped in for that. - They must have all loved you very much.
-好嗎？他們全部一起出錢買的 -他們一定都很喜歡你
Look, Ross, Sandy's just sensitive. That's all.
聽著，羅斯，珊帝只不過是很敏感 不過是如此
Okay, okay. See, that is the problem. He is too sensitive.
好了，看吧，那就是個問題 他太敏感了
Too sensitive to take care of our baby?
太敏感就不能照顧我們的小孩嗎？
No, I mean, that guy.. These are amazing!
不，我是說，那個男的… 這真是太好吃了！
Sandy made madeleines.
珊帝做的馬德琳餅乾
This is exactly what I'm talking about.
這就正是我在說的
What kind of a guy makes delicate French cookies?
什麼樣的男人會做精緻的法式餅乾呢？
They're not even butch, manly cookies with..
看起來根本不像是男性化 雄赳赳的餅乾，有那種…
You know, with chunks!
你知道的，大塊咬的快感！
Well, you know, I don't know what to say.
嗯，你知道的 我不知道能說什麼
I mean, I never thought of you as a guy who needed his men to be men.
我是說，我從沒想過你是那種 需要「男人」是真正男人的男人
I gotta tell you, Ross, it's not like you just came in from branding cattle.
我必須告訴你，羅斯 你也不像是會烙印牛只的西部牛仔
Hey, there's sensitive and there's too sensitive.
嘿，敏感跟太敏感是有區別的
Okay, what is too sensitive?
好吧，那什麼是叫做太敏感呢？
No, I can't. I can't do this. It's bad.
不，我不能，我不能這樣做，這樣不好
But it's nice. And nice is good.
但是感覺很棒，而很棒就是好
And good is not bad. Ergo, we should keep kissing.
而好就不是壞事 因此，我們應該繼續親吻
- No, no. No. - But..
-不，不，不 -但是…
Ergo.
但是什麼？
Look, David, if you had never left, then..
聽著，大衛，如果你沒有離開過…
yeah, we'd probably still be together right now.
那或許現在我們還是在一起的
But you did leave. And I'm with Mike and I really care about him.
但是你離開了，而我現在跟麥克交往 而且我很在乎他
Okay.
好的
Well, he's very lucky.
嗯，他很幸運
Thank you.
謝謝你
Goodbye.
再見
The key works.
鑰匙可以用
Hi, Mike.
嗨，麥克
And, you, thanks for the face massage! Thank you!
還有你，謝謝你的臉部按摩！ 謝謝你！
Did Rachel tell you we hired a male nanny?
瑞秋有告訴你我們雇了一個男保姆嗎？
I think that's great!
我認為那太棒了！
Did she tell you he plays the recorder, recites poetry and bakes madeleines?
她有說他會吹直笛，吟詩作對 還會做馬德琳餅乾嗎？
- How are they? - Lighter than air, but that's not the point.
-好吃嗎？ -好吃極了，但那不是重點
Rachel and I hired a male nanny.
瑞秋跟我雇了一個男保姆
Really?
真的嗎？
Guys do that?
男生會做那樣的工作嗎？
- That's weird. - Thank you!
-真是奇怪 -謝謝你！
- That's like a woman wanting to be.. - What?
-那就像是女人想要成為… -什麼？
- What's the end of that sentence? - Yes. What is the end of that sentence?
-成為什麼？ -是啊，成為什麼？
A penis model!
陰莖模特兒！
Anyway, did you tell Chandler that some guy from work..
你有告訴錢德有一個男同事…
is the funniest guy you ever met?
是你遇過最風趣的男人嗎？
- Yeah. So? - Wow!
-有啊，怎樣呢？ -哇！
Really? Do you not know Chandler?
真的嗎？你是不認識錢德嗎？
Is that why he's acting so weird? He's jealous?
這就是他最近行為詭異的原因嗎？ 他在吃醋嗎？
Oh, my God, that is crazy.
喔，我的天，這真是太瘋狂了
- It's not like I'm attracted to Jeffrey. - So what?
-又不是說我喜歡上傑佛瑞 -那又怎樣？
Being funny is Chandler's thing. Like Ross' thing is..
風趣是錢德的專長 就像羅斯的專長就是…
Science?
科學？
Academia? Being a good father?
學術？好父親？
- I can't believe he's that upset. - Are you kidding?
-我不敢相信他在不高興 -你在開玩笑嗎？
That's like Chandler saying he met someone who was more uptight than you.
這就像是錢德告訴你他遇到 比你更急躁不安的人一樣
- Excuse me? - I'm sorry. Sorry. More controlling than you.
-什麼？ -抱歉，對不起，應該是比你更控制狂
- Well, that's better. - Yeah, okay.
-嗯，好多了 -是的，好了
You have to do some damage control.
你要做一些事來彌補
Because he's feeling like..
因為他覺得…
What are you guys talking about?
你們在說些什麼？
Rachel and I hired a male nanny.
瑞秋跟我雇了一個男保姆
You got a man who's a nanny?
你雇了一個男人當保姆？
You got a "manny"?
你雇了一個「男保」？
You know, I don't mind a male nanny..
你知道的，我是不介意男保姆…
but I do draw the line at male wet nurse.
但是我倒是很介意男的擦澡護士
You are on a roll, mister!
你真是太酷了，老兄！
If I'd known you guys were coming over, I would've brought more pizza.
如果我知道你們要過來 我就會多買幾份批薩
Okay! Okay! Stop it, you! You stop it!
好了！好啦！停止，你們！ 你們停止！
What is so funny about that?
那有什麼好笑的呢？
Monica?
莫妮卡？
I don't know, it's.. Just the way you say it.
我不知道，就是… 你說的方式很好笑
I mean, you're funny. You have that funny thing. You're a funny guy!
我是說，你很風趣 你有風趣的特質，就是很風趣的人！
Did you tell her what we talked about?
你跟她說我們談過的事嗎？
So those were pity laughs? Pity laughs?!
所以那些是同情的笑聲嗎？ 同情笑聲！
Honey, listen.
親愛的，聽著
You have nothing to worry about with Jeffrey.
你根本不需要擔心傑佛瑞
Oh, yeah? Is he funnier than me?
喔，是嗎？他比我風趣嗎？
Well, you're different funny.
你們風趣的方式不同
I mean, you're more sarcastic.
我是說，你是比較挖苦式的
Well, he does bits and impressions and limericks.
嗯，他是做一些模仿跟打油詩等等的
I do limericks.
我也會打油詩啊！
There once was a man named Chandler whose wife made him die inside.
有一個叫做錢德的男的 他老婆讓他死在裡頭
Honey, you know I think you're hilarious.
親愛的，你知道我認為你超好笑的
You know that joke you told me last week?
你知道你上星期告訴我的笑話嗎？
The one about Jerry Lewis and the girl with the lazy eye.
傑瑞路易斯跟有惺忪睡眼女生的笑話
That slayed me.
那真是笑死我了
Hey! I made up that joke and told it to you.
嗨！那是我編出來告訴你的
- Not knowing when to shut up. - Yep, that's my thing.
-不知道什麼時候該閉嘴 -是的，那就是我的專長
So how many guys have your key?
有多少男人有你家的鑰匙呢？
It's not as bad as it looks.
實際情況並不像看起來這樣糟
I was saying goodbye to an old friend.
我只是在跟一個老朋友道別
Your lipstick's on his mouth.
你的口紅都在他唇上了
We just happen to wear the same shade.
我們只是剛好都用相同的口紅
No, David and I did used to go out.
不，我跟大衛以前在一起過
But years ago. And he lives in Minsk. He's only in town for a couple days.
但是是幾年前了，而且他住在明斯克 他只是回來幾天而已
- Did you..? - No. No.
-你有沒有…？ -不，不
- Kiss him? - Oh, well, yeah.
-親他？ -喔，嗯，有
Yes, but.. Look, she really likes you.
是的，但是… 聽著，她真的很喜歡你
In fact, she stopped what was a pretty amazing kiss.
事實上，她停止了一個相當美好的親吻
- David, David, David. - No, no. He should hear this.
-大衛，大衛，大衛 -不，不，他應該要知道的
I don't think you realize just how lucky you are, fella.
我不認為你知道你有多幸運，老兄
- Don't point your finger at me! - Why?
-別用手指指著我！ -為什麼？
What are you gonna do about it?
你要怎樣呢？
Well, I'll show you what I'm gonna do about it.
好的，我會讓你瞧瞧我能怎樣
- Oh, really? Really? - You want some of that?
-喔，真的嗎？真的嗎？ -你想試試看嗎？
Stop it! Stop it! Before someone gets really hurt!
停止！停止！ 在有人受傷前快停止！
Here, David, you should just go.
拿去，大衛，你應該離開了
All right.
好的
But if I ever do come back from Minsk, well, you just better watch out.
但是如果我從明斯克回來 你最好小心一點
- If I go to Minsk, you better watch out. - Oh, you're going to Minsk?
-如果我去明斯克，你也小心點 -喔，你會去明斯克嗎？
- Well, I might. - Really?
-喔，或許會 -真的嗎？
Well, if you do, come in the spring. It's just lovely there.
如果你要去，最好在春天 春天是很宜人的
I've heard that, actually.
事實上我有聽說過
Okay, well, guys?
好了，你們
- Goodbye, Phoebe. - Bye.
-再見，菲比 -再見
- Hey, what, are you kidding me? - Right-o. Right-o.
-嘿，你在開玩笑嗎？ -沒事，沒事
Take good care of her.
好好照顧她
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
我很抱歉，非常抱歉
If you want your key back, I totally understand.
如果你想拿回你的鑰匙 我完全理解
- It's never gonna happen again, right? - Right. Never. I swear.
-這不會再發生了，對不對？ -沒錯，我發誓絕不
I just want to say, if you do ever come to Minsk, that's my number.
我只想說，如果你來明斯克 這是我的號碼
We'll party up Vladnik-style.
我們可以以俄羅斯方式開派對
Yeah! All right!
是！好的！
Hey, Ross! Check it out! Sandy taught me "Hot Cross Buns"!
嘿！羅斯！快過來！ 看珊帝教我吹「甜蜜家庭」
Really? Sounded like "Three Blind Mice."
真的嗎？聽起來像是「三隻瞎眼鼠」
- "Three Blind Mice" goes like this. - I swear to God.
-「三隻瞎眼鼠」是這樣 -別逼我
- Who's up for puppets? - Me! I'm up for puppets!
-誰想要看布偶秀呢？ -我！我要看布偶秀！
Well, please welcome:
喔，請歡迎…
The Snufflebumps!
鼻塞小子！
Who wants to be Mr. Wigglemunch and who's gonna be the Grumpus?
誰想要當搖擺先生 還有誰想當小挑剔？
How exactly is a 2-month-old supposed to appreciate puppets?
一個兩歲大的嬰兒怎麼看得懂布偶呢？
Studies show that the movement and colors help their cerebral development.
研究報告顯示動作跟顏色 可以幫助大腦發展
The whimsical characters are just for us.
這些古怪的角色只是要讓我們笑而已
I want to be Mr. Wigglemunch!
我想要當搖擺先生！
Oh, my God.
喔，我的天
Well, I guess we know who's gonna be the Grumpus!
嗯，我想我知道誰要當小挑剔了！
- That was kind of rude. - Oh, I'm sorry.
-你實在是有點沒禮貌 -喔，我很抱歉
Please apologize to Sandy and the Snufflebumps for me.
請代我跟珊帝還有鼻塞小子道歉
- You know, he was just doing his job. - You know what?
-你知道的，他只是在做份內的事 -你知道嗎？
I'm sorry I'm the only one who isn't in love with Gary Poppins out there.
我很抱歉我是唯一 一個不喜歡《陳鴻作菜》的人
But I just.. I can't go through with this.
但是我只是… 我就是沒有辦法接受
- Come on. - No! You know what?
-別這樣 -不！你知道嗎？
I would never force you to hire someone you were this uncomfortable with.
我絕對不會強迫你僱用你不喜歡用的人
That's true.
那倒是真的
Thank you.
謝謝你
You want to fire him, so you have to go do it.
是你要解雇他的，你去跟他說
So you see, Wigglemunch, that's why it's important to share.
所以，搖擺先生 這就是分享的重要
I am learning so much from you.
我從你身上學到好多
Well, I'm off to Tulsa.
好了，我要去土爾沙了
So if your maitre d' friend has any funny Oklahoma jokes..
如果你的領班朋友有任何 好笑的奧克拉荷馬笑話…
tell him to e-mail me at www-dot-ha-ha-not-so-much-dot-com!
叫他寄電子郵件到 WWW點，一點都不好笑，點COM！
Honey, you can relax.
親愛的，你可以放輕鬆了
Last night at work Jeffrey told this really sexist joke.
昨晚工作時傑佛瑞說了個 很性別歧視的笑話
- After that, not so funny anymore. - Really?
-從此之後，再也沒有那麼好笑了 -真的？
See, that's the thing. You gotta keep it smart, people!
瞧，都是這樣的 要學聰明一點的！
Don't miss that flight. You know I love you.
別錯過班機，你知道我愛你
I love you too.
我也愛你
- And I like you as a friend. - Right.
-而我像朋友一樣喜歡你 -沒錯
- See you later. - See you.
-再見 -再見
- Did the guy really make that joke? - No, he still kills me.
-那個男的真的有說那個笑話嗎？ -沒有，他還是讓我捧腹大笑
Last night he had me laughing so hard, I swear a little pee came out.
我發誓昨晚他讓我笑到 真的有點尿跑出來
Here goes.
好了
I can't watch. It's like firing Elmo.
我沒有辦法看，這就像開除愛摩一樣
Sandy? Hi.
珊帝？嗨
- Hi. - We..
-嗨 -我們…
We kind of need to talk.
我們可能需要談談
I'm afraid it's not working out.
我想恐怕這樣是行不通的
I mean, Rachel and I think you are great with Emma.
我是說 瑞秋跟我認為你帶艾□實在是很棒
- We just feel.. - You! You feel!
-我們只是覺得… -你！是你覺得！
I just feel..
我只是覺得…
that the chemistry isn't right. I'm sorry.
磁場不和，我很抱歉
We're more than happy to give you a good recommendation.
我們很樂意幫你寫推薦信的
No, that's okay. I had a lot of offers from other families.
不，沒關係，我還有很多其他的家庭 要我過去幫忙
I just picked you guys because..
我挑選你們是因為…
- I liked you the best. - Oh, damn you, Geller!
-我最喜歡你們 -喔，該死的，蓋勒！
Anyway, well I'm glad there's no hard feelings.
好了，我很高興沒有任何不愉快
None at all. You need to be happy with whoever is in your home.
一點也沒有，你們需要跟一個 能相處融洽的人才行
Although, if you don't mind telling me..
不過，如果你不介意告訴我…
what was the problem? Maybe it's something I can work on in the future.
問題是出在哪裡呢？ 或許是我在將來可以改進的地方
No, you know, it's nothing you did. It's my issue.
不，不關你的事，是我的問題
What is it?
是什麼呢？
Please?
拜託？
You know, I'm just not that comfortable with a guy who's as sensitive as you.
我只不過是不習慣 跟像你一樣敏感的男人相處
That's fair.
可以諒解
Although, can I ask, why do you think that is?
但是，我可以問你為什麼會是這樣嗎？
Why? I don't know.
為什麼？我不知道
Maybe because of my father?
或許是我父親的緣故
You know, when I was growing up, he was a tough guy.
在我的成長過程中 他總是像個硬漢一樣
You know, and as a kid, I wasn't the athlete I am now.
小時候，我不像現在一樣這麼有運動感
I play squash!
我會玩壁球！
Anyway, I always got the feeling he thought I was too sensitive.
反正，我總是覺得他認為我太敏感
That must have been hard.
那一定很難受
It was hard.
的確是很難受
I remember I was in my bedroom, playing with my dinosaurs..
我記得有一次我在房間 跟我的恐龍玩…
Playing and learning.
是一邊玩一邊學習
And my father walks in and says, "What are you doing with those things?
然後我父親走了進來說 你是在跟那些東西做什麼？
What's wrong with you? Why aren't you outside playing like a real boy?"
你有什麼不對勁？為什麼你不能去外面 像真正的男生一樣玩呢？
- But you are a real boy. - I know I am!
-但是你是真正的男生啊 -我知道我是的！
And when it's summer and it's hot, why can't you wear a tank top?!
夏天很熱的時候 為什麼不能穿背心裝呢？
It's all right. Crying is good. It lets the boo-hoos out.
沒關係，哭泣是好事 大聲哭出來吧
Here comes some more!
再哭出來吧！
Emma, one day you're gonna grow up and be a big girl, just like your daddy.
艾□，有天你會長成大女孩 就跟你爹地一樣
And what's the one kind of boat that can never ever sink?
哪一種船是永遠不會沉的船呢？
- What kind? - A friend ship!
-哪一種？ -「友船」（音同友誼）！
Wow! You blow my mind!
哇！你真讓我大開眼界！
I gotta go.
我要走了
- How much do I owe you? - Twenty bucks.
-我該給你多少呢？ -二十塊
It's like the cheapest college ever!
就像是史上最便宜的大學了！
- I'll see you tomorrow. - Okay, bye-bye, Skadandy.
-明天見 -好的，掰掰，珊卡丹帝